{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow!' Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn."},{"text":"🐈 I am small and furry."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Woof! Woof!' Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones."},{"text":"🚶‍♀️ I like to go for walks."},{"text":"🐶 I am a good friend to people."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦆 I have webbed feet."},{"text":"🧡 My beak is often orange."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat plants and seeds."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I go 'Moo!' and give you milk. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I live on a farm."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat grass."},{"text":"🥛 I give you milk."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Goat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I like to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I am very big."},{"text":"🚿 I can use my trunk to spray water."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I hop and have long ears. I love carrots. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I like to eat orange vegetables."},{"text":"🐾 I have a fluffy tail."},{"text":"🐇 I am quick and like to hop around."}],"options":[{"label":"Bunny","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fox","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I have a mane and roar. I am the king of the jungle. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I live in Africa."},{"text":"🍖 I eat meat."},{"text":"👑 I am very strong."}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Wolf","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I climb trees and eat bananas. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I like to swing from branches."},{"text":"🌴 I live in the jungle."},{"text":"🍌 I peel and eat a yellow fruit."}],"options":[{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Panda","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I am black and white and live in the zoo. I like to eat bamboo. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐼 I'm a type of bear."},{"text":"⚪️ I have patches of white."},{"text":"🌱 I mostly eat bamboo."}],"options":[{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Panda","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rhino","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes and live in Africa. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 My stripes are unique, like fingerprints."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"🐴 I look a bit like a horse."}],"options":[{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Leopard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"cosmos":[{"level":"1","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm big and bright, and I shine in the day! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I make the flowers grow!"},{"text":"🔆 I am very hot!"},{"text":"⬆️ I go up, then I go down."}],"options":[{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"2","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm up in the sky, round and white! Sometimes you can see me at night. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧀 Sometimes I look like cheese."},{"text":"🌑 I change shape every night."},{"text":"🐺 Werewolves howl at me!"}],"options":[{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"3","type":"cosmos","question":"I twinkle at night, far away, up high! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✨ I'm really, really hot."},{"text":"🌟 I look small but I am very big."},{"text":"🌃 You see lots of me in the night."}],"options":[{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"4","type":"cosmos","question":"What keeps the moon and the Earth together?","hints":[{"text":"⬇️ It pulls things down"},{"text":"🍎 It made an apple fall on a head"},{"text":"🤝 It's an invisible connection"}],"options":[{"label":"Magic","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Gravity","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Friendship","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"5","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a big ball that is our home. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌍 I have lots of water."},{"text":"🏡 You live here!"},{"text":"💚 I have green grass."}],"options":[{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Earth","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"6","type":"cosmos","question":"What goes around the Earth?","hints":[{"text":"🌕 It shines at night"},{"text":"🌓 It has phases, like a circle, half-circle, then no circle!"},{"text":"🚀 Astronauts went there"}],"options":[{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The Stars","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"7","type":"cosmos","question":"If you were an astronaut in space, what would you wear?","hints":[{"text":"🪖 It keeps you safe"},{"text":"💨 It gives you air to breath"},{"text":"👨‍🚀 Neil Armstrong wore one"}],"options":[{"label":"A swimsuit","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Spacesuit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"My Pajamas","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"8","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm red and dusty, and I'm a planet too! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍫 Like the color of chocolate"},{"text":"🚀 People send robots to visit me."},{"text":"🔥 I'm the 4th planet from the Sun."}],"options":[{"label":"Jupiter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Venus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"9","type":"cosmos","question":"What do we call all the stars, planets, and moons?","hints":[{"text":"🌌 It's very, very big"},{"text":"🔭 You can see it with a telescope"},{"text":"✨ It has galaxies in it"}],"options":[{"label":"The Universe","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The Park","isCorrect":false},{"label":"My Bedroom","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}},{"level":"10","type":"cosmos","question":"What is the name for a group of many stars?","hints":[{"text":"👯 They hang out together"},{"text":"🥛 It looks like spilled milk in the night sky"},{"text":"🏘️ Our sun is one of the stars in it!"}],"options":[{"label":"A Galaxy","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Constellation","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"✨"}}]}